egrmagazine.com 2019-09-20

# Privacy | EGR | The online gaming industry’s leading information and networking group

**What is this Privacy Policy for?**

This privacy policy is for the EGR Global website and governs the privacy of the users who choose to use it.

The policy sets out the different areas where user privacy is concerned and outlines the obligations & requirements of the users, the website and website owners. Furthermore, the way EGR Global processes, stores and protects user data and information will also be detailed within this policy.

**Collection/processing of personal data**

**Phone**  
In order for EGR Global to improve customer service and provide additional training to staff, some calls may be monitored and recorded. All data subjects have the right to withdraw consent, object to processing, to request rectification/erasure through EGR Global’s data controller. See end of privacy policy for contact details.

**Data processing and acquisition**  
Your personal information is kept private and stored securely for a maximum of two years following your most recent digital interaction with EGR Global, unless required to successfully execute the terms of a contract you hold with us, as detailed in the GDPR regulation. Following the end of your contract your personal details will be retained for a maximum of two years unless digital interaction with EGR Global continues whereby your data will be stored until your most recent digital interaction exceeds two years. As part of this two-year period of no digital interaction we may provide you reasonable opportunity to opt in to further communications with EGR Global before data is removed.

Every effort has been made to ensure a safe and secure form to email submission process but advise users using such form to email processes that they do so at their own risk. Users have the right to withdraw consent, object to processing, to request rectification/erasure and submit a Subject Access Request through EGR Global’s data controller for any personal information collected. See end of the privacy policy for contact details.

**Legitimate Interest**  
EGR Global also operates data research projects to provide relevant and appropriate information to select individuals based on legitimate interest in EGR Global. Individuals are carefully selected based on detailed criteria that correctly matches products to prospects. EGR Global, in compliance with GDPR regulation, will market to prospects only targeted where a legitimate interest exists and takes a proactive approach to ensure the receiving prospects are carefully selected

“Legitimate Interests” means the interests of our company in conducting and managing our business to enable us to give you the best service/products and the best and most secure experience.

For example, we have an interest in making sure our marketing is relevant to you, so we may process your information to send you marketing that is tailored to your interests. It can also apply to processing that is in your interests as well. For example, we may process your information to protect you against fraud when transacting on our website, and to ensure our websites and systems are secure. When we process your personal information for our legitimate interests, we make sure to consider and balance any potential impact on you (both positive and negative), and your rights under data protection laws. Our legitimate business interests do not automatically override your interests – we will not use your Personal Data for activities where our interests are overridden by the impact on you (unless we have your consent or are otherwise required or permitted to by law).

We process personal information for certain legitimate business purposes, which include some or all of the following:

where the processing enables us to enhance, modify, personalise or otherwise improve our services/communications for the benefit of our customers  
to identify and prevent fraud  
to enhance the security of our network and information systems  
to better understand how people interact with our websites  
to provide postal communications which we think will be of interest to you  
to determine the effectiveness of promotional campaigns and advertising

Whenever we process data for these purposes we will ensure that we always keep your Personal Data rights in high regard and take account of these rights. You have the right to object to this processing if you wish, and if you wish to do so please get in touch with us (See contact details below). Please bear in mind that if you object this may affect our ability to carry out tasks above for your benefit.

**Events**  
EGR Global will from time to time collect sensitive personal data such as dietary requirements in order to provide a better event experience for customers. In lieu of the potential nature of this personal data extra measures are in place to ensure user privacy is respected. Personal data collected for the single purpose of the respective event in question will be deleted immediately following the conclusion of the event unless explicitly instructed not to do so by the customer. Event terms & conditions are available here.

**Contract Execution**  
In order to enter into a contract with ‘brand name’ specific user data is required to complete this contract and provide the service requested within this contract. All data collected is held securely and in compliance with GDPR regulations. Failure to supply certain personal details will prevent the ability to execute agreed contracts

**The Website**  
This website and its owners take a proactive approach to user privacy and ensure the necessary steps are taken to protect the privacy of its users throughout their visiting experience. This website complies to all UK national laws and requirements for user privacy.

**Use of Cookies**  
See our Cookie Policy page for information about how and why we use cookies (https://egr.global/cookies/ ).

Contact & Communication  
Users contacting this website and/or its owners do so at their own discretion and provide any such personal details requested at their own risk. This website operates a confirmed consent when users submit all online forms to access content via online or tailored newsletters. Your personal information is kept private and stored securely for a maximum of two years unless required to successfully execute the terms of a contract as detailed in the the GDPR regulation. Every effort has been made to ensure a safe and secure form to email submission process but advise users using such form to email processes that they do so at their own risk. Users have the right to withdraw consent, object to processing, to request rectification/erasure and submit a Subject Access Request through EGR Global’s data controller for any personal information collected. See end of the privacy policy for contact details.

This website and its owners use any information submitted to provide you with further information about the products/services they offer or to assist you in answering any questions or queries you may have submitted. This includes using your details to subscribe you to any email newsletter program the website operates but only if this was made clear to you and your express permission was granted when submitting any form to email process. Or whereby you the consumer/visitor have previously purchased from or enquired about purchasing from the company a product or service that the email newsletter relates to. This is by no means an entire list of your user rights in regard to receiving email marketing material. All data handled outside the EEA is subject to the same strict policies with appropriate contracts in place to ensure this. Your details are not passed on to any third parties. If ‘brand’ is collaborating with a third party to provide any content such as a report or webinar, you may be given the option to opt-in to receive updates from the third party but this will be explicitly stated.

**Email Newsletter**  
This website operates an email newsletter program, used to inform subscribers about products and services supplied by this website. Users can subscribe through an online automated process should they wish to do so but do so at their own discretion. Some subscriptions may be manually processed through prior written agreement with the user.

Subscriptions are taken in compliance with UK Spam Laws detailed in the Privacy and Electronic Communications Regulations 2003. All personal details relating to subscriptions are held securely and in accordance with the GDPR regulation. No personal details are passed on to third parties nor shared with companies / people outside of the company that operates this website. Under the GDPR regulation, you may request a copy of personal information held about you by this website’s email newsletter program. A small fee may be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please contact our data protection officer using the contact details at the bottom of this policy. Email marketing campaigns published by this website or its owners may contain tracking facilities within the actual email. Subscriber activity is tracked and stored in a database for future analysis and evaluation. Such tracked activity may include; the opening of emails, forwarding of emails, the clicking of links within the email content, times, dates and frequency of activity. This information is used to refine future email campaigns and supply the user with more relevant content based on their activity.

In compliance with UK Spam Laws and the Privacy and Electronic Communications Regulations 2003 subscribers are given the opportunity to unsubscribe or change your email preferences at any time through an automated system. This process is detailed at the footer of each email campaign. If an automated un-subscription system is unavailable clear instructions on how to unsubscribe will be detailed instead. You can also unsubscribe by contacting data@pageantmedia.com

**External Links**  
Although this website only looks to include quality, safe and relevant external links users should always adopt a policy of caution before clicking any external web links mentioned throughout this website.

The owners of this website cannot guarantee or verify the contents of any externally linked website despite their best efforts. Users should, therefore, note that they click on external links at their own risk and this website and its owners cannot be held liable for any damages or implications caused by visiting any external links mentioned. Upon leaving the website all users become subject to the privacy policy of that organisation.

**Adverts and Sponsored Links**  
This website may contain sponsored links and adverts. These will typically be served by our advertising partners, whom may have detailed privacy policies relating directly to the adverts they serve.

Clicking on any such adverts will send you to the advertiser’s website through a referral program which may use cookies and will tracks the number of referrals sent from this website. This may include the use of cookies which may in turn be saved on your computer’s hard drive. Users should therefore note that they click on sponsored external links at their own risk and this website and its owners cannot be held liable for any damages or implications caused by visiting any external links mentioned.

**Social Media Platforms**  
Communication, engagement and actions taken through external social media platforms that this website and its owners participate on are custom to the terms and conditions as well as the privacy policies held with each social media platform respectively.

Users are advised to use social media platforms wisely and communicate / engage upon them with due care and caution in regard to their own privacy and personal details. This website nor its owners will ever ask for personal or sensitive information directly through social media platforms, although may direct users to online forms to access additional content provided by this website. Users are encouraged to contact them through primary communication channels such as by telephone or email for users wishing to discuss sensitive details.

This website may use social sharing buttons which help share web content directly from web pages to the social media platform in question. Users are advised before using such social sharing buttons that they do so at their own discretion and note that the social media platform may track and save your request to share a web page respectively through your social media platform account.

**Shortened Links in Social Media**  
This website and its owners through their social media platform accounts may share web links to relevant web pages. By default some social media platforms shorten lengthy urls. (this is an example: http://bit.ly/zyVUBo).

Users are advised to take caution and good judgement before clicking any shortened urls published on social media platforms by this website and its owners. Despite the best efforts to ensure only genuine urls are published many social media platforms are prone to spam and hacking and therefore this website and its owners cannot be held liable for any damages or implications caused by visiting any shortened links. Users visiting external links via Social Media will then become subject to that organisation’s Privacy Policy

**Data Retention Policy**  
EGR Global operates a data retention policy that keeps your personal information private and securely stored until no longer required to execute a contract or a maximum of two years following your most recent interaction with ‘brand’. Following the end of a contract, personal details will be retained for a maximum of two years unless digital interaction with ‘brand’ continues whereby your data will be stored until your most recent digital interaction exceeds two years. As part of this two-year period of no digital interaction we may provide you reasonable opportunity to opt in to further communications with ‘brand’ before data is removed. Users have the right to withdraw consent, object to processing, to request rectification/erasure and submit a Subject Access Request through Pageant Media’s data controller for any personal information collected. See end of privacy policy for contact details.

Contacting Us  
You can contact Pageant Gaming Media via the following:

Pageant Gaming Media Holdings Ltd’s registered address is:

One London Wall

London

EC2Y 5EA

Pageant Gaming Media’s Data Protection officer role is executed by Phil O’Toole with day to day duties carried out by Hristo Gopin, Head of Data, contactable via data@pageantmedia.com

+44 0207 832 6500

Pageant Gaming Media Holdings Ltd is registered in England and Wales under registration number 08338976

Right to Lodge a Complaint  
All users have the right to lodge a complaint with the appropriate supervisory authority. All complaints can be lodged with the ICO who can be contacted at https://ico.org.uk/concerns/

Pageant Gaming Media regularly reviews its privacy policy.

This privacy policy was last updated on 22/05/2018
